#### **Contact Information**

#### **Email**

wahidpasha1997@gamil.co m

#### **Address**

#3310 6th cross cv road mandi Mohalla Mysore Karnataka india 570021

**Phone** 9901023502

Date of birth Jul 26, 1997

**Nationality** indian

## Link

https://www.linkedin.com /in/wahid-pashabb70741a8

## Skills

### Selenium

Basics of Java

**C** Programming

Hands on experience with OTN - DWDN

 $\boxtimes$  Follow the SLA for issues with respect to the severity

☑ Working quickly and effectively to take action against requests and incidents of escalated issues

☐ Effective soft skills and interpersonal skills and adept at adapting to different environments

# Languages

# **English**Intermediate

hindi

Advanced

**kannada ,urdu** Native

#### Wahid Pasha

#### **Network Administrator**

To work in a firm with Networking and IT professional with a career background of analysis work driven environment where pursuit of challenging assignments of organization in application of my technical skills, interpersonal skills, strong functional knowledge analytical abilities and expertise in making a positive difference, which would be enable my 3 years experience to grow and fulfilling organizational goal.

#### **Experience**

mysore,karnataka india Dec 2021 - Present

#### Network Administrator

## **Wipro Technologies ltd**

- Supporting Field Engineers for integration and configuration of Domain across PAN India.
- Installing up-to-date Microsoft management systems
- Provided troubleshooting on server issues reported by client
- Installation, Integration, Configuration, and proper support of Active Directories based on Windows Server
- Installation and troubleshooting of different client application software like SCCM, VPN, McAfee and Remote connectivity.
- Providing 3rd lever support to the Network Operation and implementation team.

bangluru,karnataka india Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

# • telecom engineer

#### Sanvith communication

- Installation and commissioning of Nokia DWDM equipments like (PSS-32, PSS-24, PSS-8)
- Maintained network infrastructure and resolved TCP/IP connectivity issues.
- Supported for Cisco routers and switches for Retail branch network, Securities branch network and corporate network.
- Supervised and work on different types of LAN cables.
- Provided front line telecommunication support, programming PAN India

mysore,karnataka india Feb 2018 - Aug 2018

## Internship trainee

## **1&t Technology Services**

- inspecting, testing, and updating electronic systems, components, equipment
- integration,regression testing and Debugging,trouble shooting.
- Observing existing processes and making recommendations for improvement.
- Representing the company at conferences and delivering presentations for client

bangluru,karnataka india Jan 2015 - Jan 2016

# Apprentice

# Bharat Heavy Electricals(EDN)Ltd

- leaned Functional testing and Connectivity Testing with a wiring table.
- training on High Voltage Testing, PCB Component testing and understanding p&ID's, hardware engineering and I'O
- Hands on exprience on network connection, computer operation and troubleshooting of network problems with DPU to computer

# Education

mysore,karnataka india *Mar 2016 - Oct 2021*   Bachelor of Engineering in Electronics and Communication Engineering

Mysore-ATME collage of engineering (Visvesvaraya Technological University )

 project - solar operated vision capturing spy Robot using raspberry Pi.

nanjangud karnataka india Apr 2013 - Jan 2016

# Diploma

JSS polytechnic (Department of Technical Education)

 $\label{eq:project:model} \textbf{Project}: automate street \ light \ controller \ using \ embedded \\ system$ 

# Certifications & Courses

- Completed internship course in IOT (internet of things) under ATME ECE RESEARCH CENTER, ATME College of Engineering, Mysuru Karnataka State India.
- completed Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA) with 6 months of training at Ecclesia Advanced computer technology.